<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Updates>
  <Latest version="1.8.6.0">
    <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.6</Name>
    <Description>
      Fixes issues related to launching beta versions of Operation Arrowhead and Combined Ops
    </Description>
    <ChangeLog>
      - Fixes a bug related to launching Operation Arrowhead beta versions
    </ChangeLog>
    <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML.exe</Download>
    <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1860</Info>
  </Latest>
  <Archive>
    <Application version="1.8.5.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.5</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes issues related to Operation Arrowhead and Combined Ops
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Allows Combined Ops to be launched correctly from within the launcher
        - Fixes an issue with exclude syntax which caused mods to not be excluded
        correctly.
        - Adds support for launching the games using Steam
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_185.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1850</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.8.4.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.4</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds the ability to get launch information from a server.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds ArmA2: PMC to the list of mods that cannot be loaded
        when specified by the server.
        - Will not allow you to join a server that is running Operation
        Arrowhead if you do not have it installed or are not running it.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_184.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1840</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.8.3.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.3</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds support for ArmA2 and ArmA2OA installs being in the same
        folder.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds support for ArmA 2 and ArmA 2: OA installations sharing
        a folder when Combined Operations is launched.
        This should help Sprocket users who install ArmA 2 in their
        OA folder (which results in no ArmA 2 registry key being created).
        - Attempts to fix a bug resuling in no mods being launched in certain
        cases.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_183.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1830</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.8.2.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.2</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds methods for gathering information from the server
        which the user specified for loading mods and implimenting
        other features.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds code for getting information about the server including
        the currently available mods, the number of players on the server
        etc.
        - Adds the -showserverdetails option to display information about
        the server that the user has chosen.
        - Adds the -waitforemptyslot parameter which will cause the application
        to wait for an empty slot to become available on the server before
        attempting to join it.
        - Note that this is not guaranteed to get you onto a busy server as
        there may always be someone who is quicker at clicking refresh than
        your ArmA 2 is at loading.
        - A value can be given for this parameter which will specify the amount
        of time the application will wait between each request to the server
        to check the number of players. This is measured in milliseconds.
        - If the server is currently unavailable the user may choose to wait
        for it to become available. (This is overriden by the -y switch)
        - Fixed a bug causing no missing mods to be displayed if the user had no
        mods installed or none were selected with the search.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_182.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1820</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.8.1.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.1</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds the ability to use parameter files with command
        line switches and to override options which are in the
        parameter file.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Allows paramsfile to be used with other options or on
        its own.
        - Allows options in the paramsfile to be overriden through
        the use of switches
        - Fixes possible problems with some of the command line
        option processing code which would ignore values which
        did not require an identifier if they were placed after
        a switch (which didn't need a value).
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_181.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1810</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.8.0.0">
        <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.8.0</Name>
        <Description>
          Adds options for connecting to servers
        </Description>
        <ChangeLog>
          - Adds the -server="ip:port" option to allow
          you to specify the server to connect to without
          having to use -option="-server=ip" -option="-port=port"
          - Adds the -password="" option to allow you
          to specify a password for connecting to the server
          - Just specifying -password without a value will cause
          the application to prompt you for a value at runtime.
        </ChangeLog>
        <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_180.exe</Download>
        <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1800</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.9.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.9</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes Combined Ops launching in beta mode when -beta is
        not specified.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixes Combined Ops launching in beta mode when -beta and
        -newest is not specified.
        - Fixes Google Analytics tracking event being sent when -ga=off
        is specified during an update.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_179.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1790</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.8.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.8</Name>
      <Description>
        Updates tracking code for better stability and reduced
        latency.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Updates the tracking code to run on a seperate thread
        to reduce the chances of lag on slow connections.
        - Removes a dependency on a HTTP Server file which was
        used by the previous tracking code in case that could
        be missing in certain cases.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_178.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1780</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.7.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.7</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds a fix for mod paths which have spaces in them.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds parenthesis to mod paths which contain spaces
        to prevent them from failing to load.
        - Adds a -ga=full option which will additionally report
        information about which game you are choosing to launch
        to help us track where we should be focussing development
        time. This option is disabled by default.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_177.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1770</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.6.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.6</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds Google Analytics code for application crashes in an
        attempt to make it easier for us to track the stability
        of the application. Also adds the ability to opt out of
        Google Analytics tracking.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds Google Analytics tracking code for unhandled exceptions
        to help improve the stability of release versions.
        - Adds a -ga="" option to disable Google Analytics should you
        prefer not to provide this information. You can disable it
        by adding -ga=off to your command line.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_176.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1760</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.5.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.5</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds support for launching mods from folders outside the base
        game directories.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixed incorrect location for registry items
        (Bohemia Interactive Studios -> Bohemia Interactive Studio)
        - Preliminary code for launching mods from folders outside the
        base game directory through the use of the -modfolder="" option
        (Experimental, may be removed at a later date)
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_175.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1750</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.4.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.4</Name>
      <Description>
        Major bugfix release to fix problems with launching ArmA 2
        if the ArmA 2 game path could not be found. Also adds large
        error handling code to allow for a "graceful" crash should
        a problem occur.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds checks for ArmA 2 and ArmA 2: OA paths before attempting
        to launch either game.
        - Adds global exception capture code to prevent crash dialogs
        from appearing and to give the user time to react.
        - Fixes a bug in the code that checks for ArmA 2 and ArmA 2: OA
        executable files to prevent a crash in certain cases where the
        files were missing.
        - Fixed a small problem with how the application handled missing
        registry keys but a present executable file in the current
        directory (wherever the launcher is placed) which could cause
        it to mistakenly say that the game was not present.
        (Relapse from version 1.6.0 onwards)
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_174.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1740</Info>
    </Application>
    <Latest version="1.7.3.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.3</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds Google Analytics tracking to the update function to
        better allow us to determine update statistics for the application.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds Google Analytics tracking to the application.
        - Fixes certain bugs with Registry Key handling.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_173.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1730</Info>
    </Latest>
    <Application version="1.7.2.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.2</Name>
      <Description>
        Functionality upgrade adding support for ArmA 2: Operation Arrowhead
        and ArmA 2: Combined Operations as well as fixing a few small possible
        bugs.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds -oa option to launch ArmA 2: Operation Arrowhead
        - Adds -co option to launch ArmA 2: Combined Operations
        - Fixes a possible crash should the "beta" folder not be present.
        - Adds checks to make sure that the application can in fact find
        the ArmA 2 or Operation Arrowhead executables before trying to
        launch them.
        - More robust Registry Key handling code to reduce the chances of
        a crash.
        - Adds exclusion list for default Operation Arrowhead folders.
        - Adds a check for Combined Operations to prevent the game from
        launching if ArmA 2's directory could not be found.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_172.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1720</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.7.1.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.7.1</Name>
      <Description>
        Functionality upgrade adding support for ArmA 2: Operation Arrowhead
        and ArmA 2: Combined Operations as well as fixing a few small possible
        bugs.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds -oa option to launch ArmA 2: Operation Arrowhead
        - Adds -co option to launch ArmA 2: Combined Operations
        - Fixes a possible crash should the "beta" folder not be present.
        - Adds checks to make sure that the application can in fact find
        the ArmA 2 or Operation Arrowhead executables before trying to
        launch them.
        - More robust Registry Key handling code to reduce the chances of
        a crash.
        - Adds exclusion list for default Operation Arrowhead folders.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_171.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1720</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.6.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.6.0</Name>
      <Description>
        A nother large functionality upgrade, this one adds the
        ability to launch the application with a single file as
        the parameter (without any identifier) where the file will
        act as a list of parameters (with each parameter on a different
        line). There is also the ability to copy the parameters that
        are used to launch ArmA 2 to the clipboard for use in creating
        shortcuts or in Steam.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds a -openfolder switch which will open the ArmA 2 directory
        (useful for people who use Steam where the ArmA 2 directory
        may be under C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam\steamapps\commmon\arma 2"
        - Adds a -copy switch to copy the ArmA 2 launch options to the
        clipboard for use in creating shortcuts.
        - Adds an anonymous parameter which can be used (alone) to open
        a file which holds the command line switches to be processed
        by the application. Allows you to drag and drop a file with
        a set of preset options onto the ArmA2ML executable and have
        them launched.
        - Adds a -mock switch which will allow the application to imitate
        launching ArmA 2 without performing the final launch. Useful for
        use with the -copy switch or for debuging the output.
        - Fixes some of the code to reduce the likelyhood of the wrong version
        being detected when checking for updates.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_160.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1600</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.5.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.5.0</Name>
      <Description>
        A large functionality upgrade, adds support for mod lists in
        text files as well as a -newest option to launch the latest
        version of the game (Beta or Stable).
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds support for lists of mods in a text file where each
        mod search appears on a different line. File should be
        specified with the -file="" parameter.
        - Adds a -newest switch which will launch the newest version
        of the game (Beta or Stable) based on the application build
        number. Will override -beta if both are used.
        - Adds an "explicit" option to the -engine switch. Will only search
        for mods who's names exectly match the given values (case insensitive).
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_150.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1500</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.4.1.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.4.1</Name>
      <Description>
        Quick fix for the update version in v1.4.0 appearing as v1.3.0
        causing v1.4.0 applications to think they were out of date.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Application will no longer say that it is out of date when
        running the latest version.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_141.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1410</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.4.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.4.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This release adds the ability to disable coloured text
        in the console.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - nocolour switch added to disable colours in the console
        for people who prefer the default colours.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_140.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1400</Info>
    </Application>
    <Application version="1.3.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.3.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This release adds the ability to specify the search
        engine that you would like to use when specifying mod
        directories.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - engine parameter added to allow the user to specify
        the search engine to be used when looking for mod
        directories.
        - RegEx will provide a more powerful search platform
        however normal search will allow the application to
        be more usable for people without knowledge of RegEx.
        - If engine is not specified it will default to RegEx to
        preserve compatibility with startup commands from
        previous versions.
        - Changed icon size to reduce EXE size by around 270KB for
        quicker downloading and updating. (330KB -> 60KB)
        - Numerous update fixes added, should be more reliable now.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_130.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1300</Info>
    </Application>    
    <Application version="1.2.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.2.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This release adds support for self-updating over the
        internet as well as a few stability fixes and additional
        startup parameters.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Will not allow system directories (ArmA 2) to be
        added as mods (e.g. AddOns)
        - About page and Help page will now show the Sierra Softworks
        project page's address
        - Added -web argument for displaying Sierra Softworks
        project page
        - Added support for self-updating to the latest version
        - Added backup of old versions during update in case of
        failure.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_120.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1200</Info>
    </Application>    
    <Application version="1.1.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.1.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This is the second release of ArmA 2 Mod Launcher.
        It adds numerous fixes and usability enhancements as 
        well as a revised search system.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Now uses RegEx for parsing command line arguments
          - Now accepts command line arguments in the 
            following forms:
              + -arg value
              + /arg value
              + --arg value
              + arg:value
              + /arg:value
              + --arg:value
              + -arg=value
              + /arg=value
              + --arg=value
        - Allows ! prefix for exclusion searches
          - e.g. "-mod=!ACE" will exclude mods with the word 
                 ACE in their name
        - Revised logic to make use of updated command line 
          parsing
        - Colour text in console for enhanced readability
        - Updated -help and -about options
        - Highlights missing mods
        - Highlights mods that are selected more than once 
          by the search(es).
        - Added -y option to disable prompts for the user.
        - Added -silent option to disable text.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/arma2ml/ArmA2ML_110.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml/updates/1100</Info>
    </Application>    
    <Application version="1.0.0.0">
      <Name>ArmA 2 Mod Launcher v1.0.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This is the initial release of ArmA 2 mod launcher.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download></Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/arma2ml</Info>
    </Application>
  </Archive>
</Updates>
